I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Fishing Hole"
（ミッちゃん）お～い
Hey! The thing you asked
your friend for came!
（ミッちゃん）知り合いに
頼んでたやつが上がってきたぞ～
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）あ～ アレね
Oh that. You brought it for me.
わざわざ持ってきてくれたのか
ま～な
お前らの喜ぶ顔が見たくてさ
Yeah...
I wanted to see the joy in your face.
Hmm...
ハハ… おもしれえじゃん
This is great.
（泉(いずみ)）真帆(まほ)ちゃん… だよね？
You're Maho-chan, right?
Huh?
泉ちゃん… だっけ？
And you were...Izumi-chan?
（男性）パンツにさ—
“アイラブニューヨーク”って
書いてあったのかよ
And it says, "I love New York."
（女性）うん そんでフロア降りて
逃げるとこ 触っちった！
And I got to touch him
when he was running away.
（男性）え!? 掟(おきて)さんに触ったの？
いいな～
Huh? You touched him?
Neat!
話したいことがあるんだ
I wanted to talk to you.
今 時間はあるかな？
Do you have some time now?
（真帆）ないね
Nope.
（泉）そう… ん～
Oh...
Hmm...Ten minutes is all I need.
10分でいいから！
お茶 おごるよ
Tea? My treat.
（竜介）俺は お前と真帆の間に
何があったか知らないし—
I don't know what happened
between you and Maho.
干渉する気もない
And I don't care.
でもさ… なあ コユキ
But...
Hey Koyuki...
見た目は強く見えるヤツほど
実は弱いもんなんだぜ
The stronger a person looks,
the weaker he is.
ああ見えて 真帆のヤツさ—
Maho looks strong,
いつも家では泣いてばっかなんだ
but at home, she cries all the time.
ま～な 俺がさ
どうこう言う話じゃないけどな
Anyway, I have no right to lecture you.
よっと…
Go!
で お前 妹のこと
どう思ってんだよ？
So what...how do you feel
about my kid sister?
（千葉(ちば)）あれ～？
コユキはどうした？
Huh?
Where's Koyuki?
（竜介）ああ？
真帆を捜しに行った
Huh? He went to look for Maho.
Huh?
（竜介）真帆のヤツ
ビデオ返しに行ったまま—
Maho went to return a video
and hasn't returned for three hours.
３時間も帰って来ねえからさ
（千葉）ま～ほ～？
Maho?
ん？ まさか大事なミーティングを
すっぽかしてデートか？
Don't tell me he's gonna miss
this important meeting for a date!
（平(たいら)）あ？ デート？
（千葉）ん～ おのれコユキ…
-Huh? Date?
-That Koyuki!
（サク）あ これ お土産
Here...I brought something.
（竜介）お サンキュ！
Thanks.
（コユキ）ハァ ハァ ハァ…
"Neighborhood Watch-
Work together to prevent crime"
"Liquor, Cigarettes"
"Exciting Town"
Uh?
Huh?
（女性）あら？
じゃあね コユキ
See you, Koyuki.
Huh? Izumi-chan...
泉ちゃん…
さよなら コユキ
Good-bye, Koyuki.
（真帆）日本人の感覚って
分かんないな
I don't understand Japanese thinking.
Huh?
（真帆）彼女 わざわざ
言いに来てくれたんだよ
She hunted me down just to tell me...
自分とコユキは
本当に何でもないって
that there's nothing between you and her.
（真帆）初めはさ—
At first I thought,
"What the hell do you want?"
何しに来やがったんだ
コンニャロウ って思ったんだけど
After talking to her...
man, she's really nice.
話してみたらさ
すげえいい人じゃん
But she seems more like your older sister.
でもさ あの人は
コユキのお姉さんって感じだよね
フフ… ハンバーガー食べてくか？
Want to go eat a burger?
Err...no. Ryusuke was worried.
あ いや…
竜介君が心配してたよ
え マジ？
No shit?
えっ でもさ あいつ
そんな兄貴らしいことって…
But he never acts like a big brother...
（平）また その記事か…
Not that article again?
Why're you so stuck on it?
何でそんなにこだわるんだ？
ある時期 エディとエリカは
付き合ってたんだ
At one time, Eddy and Erica used to date.
俺たちは
たまたま遊びに行った—
We had gone to the
Appollon Theater Amateur Night
アポロンシアターの
アマチュアナイトで—
and saw Erica before she debuted.
デビュー前のエリカを見たんだ
エリカの圧倒的な歌唱力に
鳥肌が立った
Her powerful singing voice blew me away.
わざわざ出待ちをしたのは
あとにも先にも あのときだけさ…
That was the one and only time
we ever waited for someone backstage.
結局 エディとエリカの２人は
いろんな障害を越えられなくてな
But Eddy and Erica couldn't
get past their problems.
短期間で別れたんだ
Their relationship didn't last long.
あんなふうに
人にバイブを伝えられる人間が—
To think that someone
who had such strong vibes
あっけなく自殺だなんて…
俺には考えられないんだ
would commit suicide like that...
I just can't believe it.
（千葉）ん～…
なら他殺ってことか？
Hmm...
You think it was murder?
（平）ＦＢＩが怪しいとか
言われてるしな
Even the FBI is suspicious.
（竜介）エリカが死んで
一番 得してるヤツだ
And the one who benefited most
from Erica's death...
Hmm...
（平）恋人のラッパー マルコム
The rapper boyfriend...Malcolm.
（竜介）はい…
どうもすいませんでした
Yes. Thank you.
Man, it's totally over.
全滅だな
Hey, are you serious?!
おいおい マジかよ～
それじゃ メジャーからの話は…
Then that offer from major label...
世の中
そんなに甘くないってことだな
Just means life ain't so easy.
ん そうだ おい！
Wait! I know! Your letters
made the record company mad!
お前の対応が レコード会社の
怒りを買ったんじゃねえだろうな！
Huh?
Well look...During Dying Breed's
live performance, everything seemed fine!
だってよ～
ダイブリのライブんときゃ—
どこもかしこも
かなりいい感じだったじゃねえか
Well probably...Ran's power
is greater than we thought.
たぶん 俺たちが思っているより
蘭(らん)の力は大きいんだ
あいつか!?
Him?
I get it. So that's how it is.
なるほど… そういうことか
ベルアームのデビューが
台なしになった上に—
On top of losing the debut
for Belle Ame, he became a back-up.
引き立て役になっちゃったからね
相当 頭に来てるんじゃないかな
He must be mad as hell.
We got ourselves some enemy.
（平）俺たちは かなりやっかいな
ヤツを敵に回したみたいだな
Nah...We just didn't have it.
（竜介）なーに
俺たちの実力不足ってことさ
フンッ
悪かったな！
英語の発音がお粗末でさ！
Excuse me for having
a bad English accent!!
お前には進歩の跡がない！
You just don't progress!
しかも適当にごまかすくせがある
And you have a habit of mouthing off!
やっぱり 英語にカタカナのルビを
振るのには限界が…
-I think adding so many
notes about pronunciation...
-Don't lecture me!
（千葉）おめえに
言われたくねえよ
おい 竜介 練習ばかりで
モチベーションも下がり気味だぜ
Hey Ryusuke...We've been practicing
so much, our motivation is down.
When are we going to record?
一体 いつ
レコーディングするつもりなんだ？
（サク・コユキ）
えっ レコーディング!?
-Huh? Record?!
俺たちは
業界が認めざるをえない—
We have to record the ultimate album,
one the industry won't be able to ignore.
最高のアルバムを
作んなきゃなんねえんだ
（竜介）適当に妥協してちゃ—
If we sit on our asses,
we'll never reach our dream!
それなりのもんしか
手に入んねえぜ！
What?
（田辺(たなべ)）でえ～！ 今週も土曜の夜
オールでスタジオ練習だって!?
An all-night practice at
the studio again on Saturday night?!
-Uh-huh.
（田辺）お前ら 生き急いでるね～
You guys are in such a rush.
Think so? It's been the norm lately.
そう？ 最近じゃ普通なんだけど
-Right?
-Yeah.
（田辺）へえ～
頑張ってんだな お前ら
Hmm...You're really working hard, huh?
Huh?
（田辺）おい 有名になったら
サインしてくれよな ウハハ…
But hey, when you're famous,
I want your autographs.
"Really working hard" huh?
頑張ってる か…
（女子生徒１）あの人じゃない？
Isn't that him?
Yeah! He was great
at the Culture Festival.
（女子生徒２）うんうん
文化祭すごかったよね
（女子生徒３）ライブハウスとかにも
出てるらしいよ
I heard he performs at various live houses.
Huh?
（女子生徒たち）キャー フフフ…
（町田(まちだ)）おい 田中！
（コユキ）はっ
Hey Tanaka!
Come to my office.
ちょっち 職員室に来なさい
"Teachers' Office"
Huh!? That much?
（コユキ）え… そんなに…
Is it a shock?
（町田）ショックか しかし
それが今のお前の現実なんだ
But that's the reality for you right now.
Oh...
（町田）太刀(たち)高は無理
Tachi High is impossible.
Toyonaga West is also a far reach.
豊永西(とよながにし)も かな～りデンジャラス！
ああ… はい…
Err...I see.
I'll get right to the point.
（町田）はっきり言おう
You need to change your focus.
志望校の変更が必要だ
（町田）これまで 中の上を
維持してきたお前の成績が—
You were once in the high middle ranking.
Recently, you've plunged.
ここにきてガタ落ちしてる
（町田）田中
青春を謳歌(おうか)するのもいいが—
Tanaka, it's fine to enjoy your youth.
ここにきての選択は
お前の人生を左右しかねないぞ
But the rest of your life is on the line.
Yukio! It's late! Turn down the volume.
（コユキの母）幸雄～
もう遅いんだから 音小さくしな
All right.
（コユキ）は～い
（斎藤(さいとう)）うお～っ！
フンッ！ コユキ君
こんな具合に 108回だ！
Koyuki-kun! Just like this-108 laps!
It's impossible.
無理です
I gave up in four.
（コユキ）よ ４回で
ギブアップです～
No!
か～っ！ コユキ君！
Koyuki-kun! You must do your best,
or your dreams will never come true!
バリバリに気合いが入ってないと
願いは叶わないぞ！
（コユキ）はい…
I know.
（斎藤）俺は オリンピック候補に
なったときと—
Just like when I made it
on the Olympic team...
売れっ子ホステスに告白したときに
これを実践した～！
when I declared my love
to that pretty bar hostess...
I put my mind to it!
And...your dream came true?
願いは 叶ったんですね？
（斎藤）ん まあ…
これはこれ え～ それはそれ
Well...The past is the past
and the present is the present.
Huh?
見事に あっけなく 夢はついえた…
My dream came true splendidly.
俺 帰る…
I'm...going home.
So warm!
あったけ～
あ～ まったくよ～
Cripes! Ryusuke is such a perfectionist!
竜介の完璧主義は異常だぜ
He's gonna die all alone
when he's old and gray.
あいつ 絶対 晩年
孤独な死を迎えるな うん
Huh?
病院…
The hospital...
Hey!
He can't handle an all-nighter.
オールナイトは無理だと思う
死ぬぞ マジで
You'll die, for real!
No...
うん… でも 今 大事なときだから
It's an important time right now.
I can't let the band down.
バンドに迷惑かけたくないんだ
-Hmm...
（BECK(ベック)の演奏）
よし もう１度
All right, once more.
Hey! What're you doing, Koyuki?
（竜介）おい！
何やってんだ コユキ！
お前のせいで 全然
先に進めねえじゃねえか
There's been no improvement 'cuz of you!
（コユキ）ご… ごめんなさい…
I-I'm sorry.
Hey, hey!
そうだな…
ちょっと 休憩挟むか？
Look, let's take a break.
（竜介）う～ん…
サク もう１度 最初から頼む
Uh-uh...Saku, take it from the top.
One, two!
ワン ツー！
Where is this?
（コユキ）ここは… どこだ？
Where...
ここは…
Oh. Made a big mess.
（ジョン・レノン：英語）
〈あぁ こんなに汚しちゃって〉
Too sad.
〈悲しいなぁ〉
I'll help.
（サク）僕も手伝います！
I'm cleaning up the mess
your concert had made.
〈僕は君のコンサートの
後片付けをしてるのさ〉
ハァ…
When I woke up, my fever, which had
been as high as 103, had gone down.
（コユキ）眠りから覚めたとき—
39度６分もあった熱は
完全に下がっていた
And Beck's first album was completed
around the middle of winter break.
（コユキ）そして BECKの
最初のアルバムが完成したのは—
冬休みも半ばを過ぎたころだった
（ステレオ）♪「SPICE OF LIFE」
Uh! Typhoon! Typhoon 24! 24-7, non-stop!
We're gonna rush at you!
Gonna send you flyin'!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
You'll feel totally loose...
すごいね…
Isn't it great?
Yeah.
（コユキ）ふと 思った…
And I thought...
俺は将来 何をしているんだろう
What will I be doing with my life?
Koyuki?
（サク）コユキ？ どうかした？
Something up?
（コユキ）ううん 何でもない
Nah...Nothing.
But Saku, have you been studying?
でさ～ サクは勉強してんの？
いや 全然
Not at all.
（コユキ）ホントに勉強してない？
You really haven't been studying?
（サク）うん ホントにホントに
してないよ～
Yup...I really, really
haven't been studying.
（コユキ）すべては…
この１枚のＣＤから始まったんだ
Everything began with this one CD.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
It's almost over!
Let's run towards the sun!
（千葉）最後のさ～
グラスが太陽にこう
まぶしくてさあ～
It's blinding!
I wanna be Alain Delon!
アラン・ドロンに
なりたい！